Guide to the K. Leroy Irvis Papers, 1946-1995 AIS.1971.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Personal, 1939-2006; II.
  - Personal (2010 Addition), 1938-2006; 8.
    - K. Leroy Irvis Office Building, 2003 (Box 90, Folder 44)
    - Lincoln University, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 45)
    - Lion of Pennsylvania, 2003, undated (Box 90, Folder 46)
    - Marriage Certificate, 1945 (Box 90, Folder 47)
    - Masonic Lodge, 1991-1995 (Box 90, Folder 48)
    - Membership Cards and Name Badges, 1975-1997 (Box 90, Folder 49)
    - Membership Cards and Name Badges, 1967-2002 (Box 90, Folder 50)
    - Men and Steel, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Model Airplanes, 1986-1992 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Model Aviation, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Model Engines, 1984-1997 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Negro Folk Tales, 1938 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - New York Folklore Quarterly, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Notes, 1940s (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Notes, 1950s (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Notes, undated (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Notes, undated (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Notes, undated (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Notes, undated (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Notes, undated (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Notes, undated (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Obituary, 2006 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Passports, 1972-1994 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Pennsylvania Art Education Association, 1995 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Pennsylvania Tercentenary, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Pittsburgh Council for the Arts, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Poetry for Critique, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - Poetry from Dorothy Blackwell and Travis Pumphrey, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - Poetry, the Look the Feel of Cotton, undated (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - Politicians, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - R/C Organizations, 1982-1997 (Box 91, Folder 24)
    - Shrine of St. Benedict, undated (Box 91, Folder 25)
    - Sketches, undated (Box 91, Folder 26)
    - Sketches of Irvis, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 27)
    - Society of Sculptors, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 28)
    - Speakers' Portraits, 1993 (Box 91, Folder 29)
    - State University of New York (SUNY) Albany, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 30)
    - Starsburg Railroad, undated (Box 91, Folder 31)
    - Template, 1971 (Box 91, Folder 32)
    - Tennyson House, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 33)
    - Tribute by Sherri, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 34)
    - University of Pittsburgh Commencement, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 35)
    - Urban League of Pittsburgh, 1945 (Box 91, Folder 36)
    - Venable, Sateria, 1992 (Box 91, Folder 37)
    - Walker, Leona, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 38)
    - Who's Who, 1976-1977 (Box 91, Folder 39)
    - Who's Who Among Black Americans, 1975-1976 (Box 91, Folder 40)
    - Who's Who in America, 1982-1983 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Wood Carving, 2005 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Woodworking, 2002, undated (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - the Wrath of Agnes, 1972 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Yearbook, 1938 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Poetry (2010 Addition), 1919-1993; 9.
    Irvis took great interest in poetry and composed a large amount of it. Some of his compilations of poetry include This Land of Fire and Lions and Great Bronze Bars. There are various editions of each of these within this subseries, as well as manuscript editions. In addition to full compilations of poetry, this subseries also contains loose poems completed by Irvis with some accompanying handwritten notes. This subseries is arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Annotated Poetry, undated (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Assorted Poetry, undated (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Early Poetry, 1919-1943 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Hughes, Langston, undated (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Lions and Bars, Original Manuscript with Edits, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Lions and Bars, Original Manuscript with Edits, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Lions and Great Bronze Bars, manuscript, undated (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Lions and Great Bronze Bars, selections, undated (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - Lions and Great Bronze Bars, noted, undated (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Temple University Poetry Reading, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - This Land of Fire, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - This Land of Fire, annotated, 1985 (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - This Land of Fire, Correspondence and Translation with David Gould, 1985, 1987 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - This Land of Fire, Description, undated (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - This Land of Fire, manuscript, undated (Box 95, Folder 23)
    - This Land of Fire, notes on Dr. David Gould and translations, undated (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - This Land of Fire, final copy, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - This Land of Fire, Poetry Reading, undated (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - This Land of Fire, unpublished with note from H. William Deweese, Speaker, 1993 (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - This Land of Fire, Wagger's Copy, undated (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - Africa, (2010 Addition), 1947-1985; 10.
    Irvis took several trips to African countries, including the Central African Republic, and the Cote d'Ivoire. This subseries documents these trips, as well as Irvis's research on the conditions and history of these areas and information Irvis gathered about investing in Africa as part of a Pan-African business venture. The subseries is arranged alphabetically.
    - C.A.R., Cameroon, Cote d' Ivoire, 1985 (Box 112, Folder 59)
    - Cote d' Ivoire, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Department of State Background Information, 1972-1974 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Economic Trends, 1973-1974 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Human Rights, undated (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - International Business Associates, 1976 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Investing in Africa, Information, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Investing in the Ivory Coast, undated (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Mineral Surveys, undated (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - National Bank of Malawi, undated (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Overseas Business Reports, 1963-1974 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Overseas Private Investment Corporation, undated (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Pan-Africa, 1947 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Pan-African Business Ventures, 1975 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Research, undated (Box 113, Folder 14)
- Legislative Files, 1865-2006; IV.
  This series contains information on legislation that Irvis supported or introduced during his career in the Pennsylvania House of Representatives. It contains Irvis's statements, speeches and remarks about many legislative issues, as well as memoranda, correspondence, notes, and reports pertaining to legislation. In addition, the series documents Irvis's committee and leadership work in the Pennsylvania House of Representatives through items such as House calendars, documentation of legislative commissions, information on standing committees and membership lists.
  The series is divided into three subseries based on the date the material was acquired by the University of Pittsburgh: the first from the original 1971 deposit, the second from the 1980 addition, and the third from the 2010 addition.
  Supporting materials, including contemporaneous newsclippings, may be found in Series XVI: Media and in the scrapbooks in Series XVII, Subseries 3: Realia.
  - Legislative Files (1971 Original Deposit), 1951-1971; 1.
    This subseries contains legislation introduced in the Pennsylvania House of Representatives including health, welfare, education, and government resolutions. House calendars and statements, speeches, and remarks by Irvis along with House offices held by Irvis and Committees and Commissions on which he served are included in this series. Series II is arranged alphabetically, by subject, except for the House calendars (Boxes 4-5) which are arranged by date. The House calendars are personal copies of bills introduced with holograph notes written by Irvis.
    - Legislation Introduced
      - Civil Rights, 1951-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Constitutional Revision, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Consumer Protection, 1965, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Crime, juvenile delinquency, penal institutions, probation, etc., 1959-1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Education
        - Primary, secondary, 1963-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
        - Higher, secondary, 1961-1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
        - Higher, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
        - For the Handicapped, 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
        - Libraries, museums, foundations, etc., 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 16)
        - Professional licensure, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Electoral process, 1967-1971 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Family (adoption, divorce), 1969, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Food, drug, pest control, 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Government
        - Local, 1961-1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        - State, 1964-1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
        - State-Finances (appropriations, public debt, etc.), 1961-1971 (Box 2, Folder 23)
        - State-Legislature, 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Health and Welfare
        - Public assistance (including blind, aged, etc.), 1965-1971 (Box 2, Folder 25)
        - Public health, health facilities, research, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 26)
        - Mental health, mental retardation, 1961-1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Housing, urban renewal, local economic redevelopment, 1959-1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Insurance, 1967-1971 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Judiciary-Local, 1963-1969 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Judiciary-State, 1962-1971 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Labor-Public employees-Wages, retirement, collective bargaining, 1963-1971 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Labor-Wages, benefits, etc., 1963-1971 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - Military and veterans, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - Natural resources, conservation, pollution, 1966-1971 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Public utilities, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Taxation, 1962-1971 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Transportation, 1961-1971 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Miscellaneous, 1963-1971 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Major bills sponsored by KLI, compilation, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Resolutions Introduced in House
      - Personal resolutions, 1964-1969 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - States' rights, #9, 10, 11, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 42-43)
      - Station WXUR, Media, PA, investigation, #160, #12, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - Miscellaneous resolutions, 1965-1970 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - House Calendars
      - January 28 - March 26, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - April 15 - May 27, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 47-48)
      - June 2 - June 18, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - June 23 - July 30, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - September 8 - October 21, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - November 5 - December 31, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - January 6 - February 26, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 53-54)
      - March 2 - April 29, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - June 8 - June 30, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - July 7 - September 22, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - November 9 - November 19, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - Miscellaneous status of bills, legislation pending, etc., 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - House Offices, (chronological)
      - Minority Caucus Chairman, Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 60)
      - Majority Caucus Chairman, 1965-1966
        - Inter-govt. office correspondence and enclosures; Legislative Directory; Newsclippings (Box 6, Folder 61)
        - Appropriations Committee correspondence, clips (Box 6, Folder 62)
        - Correspondence of relative importance, pertaining to office, re specific legislation, or originated by KLI (Box 6, Folder 63)
        - General correspondence (Box 6, Folder 64)
      - Minority Whip, 1967-1968
        - Inter-govt. office correspondence and enclosures (Box 6, Folder 65)
        - Correspondence, notes, etc., re Democratic minority (Box 6, Folder 66)
        - Correspondence of relative importance, etc. (Box 6, Folder 67)
        - General correspondence (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - Majority Leader
        - Inter-govt. office correspondence and enclosures, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 69)
        - Legislative Committees correspondence, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 70)
        - Democratic (party) Committee correspondence, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 71)
        - Correspondence of relative importance, etc., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 72)
        - Citizen Correspondence and ecls. Re income tax., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 73)
        - Correspondence, news clips, re "retirement", 1969 (Box 7, Folder 74)
        - General correspondence, January - March, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 75)
        - General correspondence, April - December, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 76)
        - Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 77)
        - Correspondence (1 letter only), 1971 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Standing Committees
      - Membership Lists, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Legislative Commissions
      - Joint State Government Commission
        The first two objects contained under the Joint State Government Commission are notebooks pertaining to the executive committee, January 29, 1963-January 29, 1964; and February 21, 1964-November 18, 1966.
        - Joint State Government Commission Activities, 1963-65 (Box 8, Folder 80)
        - Task Force on Admission Policy of Schools of Medicine, Dentistry, and Nursing: Report drafts, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 81)
        - Miscellaneous, research reports, 1963-1970 (Box 8, Folder 82)
        - Miscellaneous correspondence and enclosures, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Budget and Finance Committee
        - Annual reports, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 84)
        - Department of Revenue memos, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 85)
        - Miscellaneous Reports, 1963-? (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - KLI statements, speeches, remarks - House
      - Miscellaneous Legislative Journals
        - 1959-1961, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 87)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 88)
        - 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 89)
        - 1971 (Box 8, Folder 90)
        - Miscellaneous, 1963?-1971? (Box 8, Folder 91-92)
  - Legislation (1980 Addition), 1963-1976; 2.
    This subseries includes the text of bills and resolutions on which Irvis worked and voted during his time in the Pennsylvania House of Representatives between 1963 and 1987, as well as correspondence relating to those pieces of legislation. This series is arranged chronologically.
    - 1963-1964 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - 1967-1969 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - 1972-1976 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Education Programs (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Legislative (2010 Addition), 1865-2006; 3.
    The material in this subseries pertains to Irvis' career as a member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives (1959-1988). During the span of his legislative career, he assisted with the introduction of a massive amount of legislation into the Pennsylvania House of Representatives. Some of this legislation is documented in this subseries in the form of a finalized House or Senate Bills and resolutions. Along the lines of legislation, Irvis collected information on Pennsylvania specific issues including Home Rule and the potential increase of the personal property tax; as well as how both issues adversely affected constituents.
    The subseries also contains materials Irvis accumulated during his routine work day. These materials include House memorandums, yearly calendars, and staff communications. In relation to his legislative career, Irvis went on several trips which are documented in this subseries. This subseries is arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - A People's Dinner Party, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 51)
    - A People's Dinner Party, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 52)
    - A People's Dinner Party, Financial, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 53)
    - ACT 101, 1981, 1983 (Box 100, Folder 54)
    - Advisory Committee on Probation, 1971 (Box 100, Folder 55)
    - Allegheny County Board of Commissioners, 1981 (Box 100, Folder 56)
    - Allegheny Legislative Delegation Office, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 57)
    - Bicentennial Legislative Session, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 58)
    - Biographical Dictionary of Early Pennsylvania Legislators, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 59)
    - Biography, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 60)
    - Black Legislators in Pennsylvania, 1911-2000 (Box 100, Folder 61)
    - Black Legislators in Pennsylvania History, 1911-1993 (Box 100, Folder 62)
    - Budget Hearing Schedule, 1997-1998 (Box 100, Folder 63)
    - Calendars, 2005, 2006 (Box 100, Folder 64)
    - Capitol Preservation Committee Report, 2002 (Box 100, Folder 65)
    - Commission on the Operation of the House, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 66)
    - Committee to Re-Elect K. Leroy Irvis, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 67)
    - Commonwealth Court of Pennsylvania, 1975-1976 (Box 100, Folder 68)
    - Commonwealth Lecture Series, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Concord Resources Group, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Congressional Recognition, 2003 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Contact Information, undated (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Council of State Governments Eastern Regional Conference, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Department of Aging, undated (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Department of Revenue, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Election Brochures, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Electoral College, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Employee Requests, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Events, 1984-2005 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Fact Sheet 110, 1980 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Fact Sheet 112, 1980 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Financial Aid for Higher Education, 1978-1979 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Financial Aid for Higher Education, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Freedom Corner, 2000 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Governor's Health Task Force, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Governor's Local Tax Reform Proposal, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - Government Relations Committee, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - Gubernatorial Inauguration, 2003 (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - Health Education Programs, State Regulation, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 21)
    - History Makers, Senate Recognition, 2005 (Box 101, Folder 22)
    - Home Rule, 1992-1995 (Box 101, Folder 23)
    - Home Rule, 1974, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 24)
    - Home Rule Data, 1997-1998 (Box 101, Folder 25)
    - H.B. 55, 1997 (Box 101, Folder 26)
    - H.B. 77, 2003 (Box 101, Folder 27)
    - H.B. 1213, 1971 (Box 101, Folder 28)
    - H.B. 1817, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 29)
    - H.B. 1883, 1993 (Box 101, Folder 30)
    - H.B. 1852, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 31)
    - H.B. 1973, 1999 (Box 101, Folder 32)
    - H.B. 2059, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 33)
    - H.B. 2061, 1980 (Box 101, Folder 34)
    - H.B. 2073, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 35)
    - H.B. 2045, undated (Box 101, Folder 36)
    - H.R. 237, 1980 (Box 101, Folder 37)
    - Individual and Family Resources in Pennsylvania, undated (Box 101, Folder 38)
    - Institute of Politics, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 39)
    - K. Leroy Irvis Office Building Dedication, 2003 (Box 101, Folder 40)
    - The Irvis Report, 1976-1982 (Box 101, Folder 41)
    - Kosmos Cement Company, 1992 (Box 101, Folder 42)
    - Legislative School Art Exhibit, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 43)
    - Legislative Initiative Program, 1992 (Box 101, Folder 44)
    - Legislative Journal, House of Representatives, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 45)
    - Legislative Journal, Senate, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 46)
    - Legislative Office for Research Liaison, 2000 (Box 101, Folder 47)
    - Legislative Office for Research Liaison, Minority Inquiry, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 48)
    - Los Angeles Riots, 1992 (Box 101, Folder 49)
    - Matthew J. Ryan Legislative Office Building, 1999 (Box 101, Folder 50)
    - Mayor's Task Force on Racial Disorder, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 51)
    - Membership Cards, 1977-1984 (Box 101, Folder 52)
    - Membership Lists, 1979-1981 (Box 101, Folder 53)
    - Memorandums, undated (Box 101, Folder 54)
    - Memorial, 1984, 2003 (Box 101, Folder 55)
    - Memorial Addresses, David P. Richardson Jr., 1995 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - National Conference of State Legislators, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - News Digest, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Newsletters, 1981, undated (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Organized Crime Report, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Panama Trip, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Panama Trip, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Panama Trip, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Park & Ride Inc., 1981 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania Bulletin, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania's Capitol, undated (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Pennsylvania's Constitutional Convention, 1967-1968 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Pennsylvania's Economy League, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, Committees, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, Film, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, General Assembly, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, General Assembly, Bicentennial Joint Session, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, Legislative Directory, 1959 (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, Legislative Directory, 1977-1978 (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, Legislative Directory, 1987-1988 (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, Publications, undated (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, Publications, undated (Box 102, Folder 22)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, Publications, undated (Box 102, Folder 23)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, House Resolution, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 24)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, Speaker's Ball, 2005 (Box 102, Folder 25)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, Speakers' Portraits, 1993-1996 (Box 102, Folder 26)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, Swearing in Ceremonies, 1997-2004 (Box 102, Folder 27)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, Testimonial, undated (Box 102, Folder 28)
    - Pennsylvania Human Relations Commission, 1995-1996 (Box 102, Folder 29)
    - Pennsylvania Human Relations Commission, 1999-2000 (Box 102, Folder 30)
    - Pennsylvania Legislative Black Caucus, 1985-2001 (Box 102, Folder 31)
    - Pennsylvania Legislative Black Caucus, Swearing In, 1997 (Box 102, Folder 32)
    - Pennsylvania Report, 1995, 1997 (Box 102, Folder 33)
    - Pennsylvania State Ethics Commission, 1991-1992 (Box 102, Folder 34)
    - Personal Property Tax, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 35)
    - Personal Property Tax, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Personal Property Tax, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh Convention-Exposition Center, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Presidential Visits, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Press Releases, 1972-1989 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Prison Disturbances and Riots, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Public Announcement, 1978 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Public Participation Committee, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Reception, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Report to the Governor, 1989-1990 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Report to the People, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Rules of Criminal Procedure, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Rules of the House of Representatives, 1999 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Schedules, 1978, 1979, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Seminar, Women at Work, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - S.B. 68, 1968 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - S.B. 178, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - S.B. 1227, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - S.B. 1367, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Senate Bill History, 1975-1976 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Senate Issue Paper, undated (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - South America Trip, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - South America Trip, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - South America Trip, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - Supreme Court, Disciplinary Board, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - State Equal Rights Convention, 1865 (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - Three Rivers Improvement and Development Corporation, 1972 (Box 103, Folder 27)
    - Union of South Africa, Statement, undated (Box 103, Folder 28)